Are you a racist party? Are you involved in a racist party?
No. We're not a racist country, Brian. We've never been a racist country.
Our goal is to make sure that today is better than yesterday.
Are we perfect? No.
But our goal is to always make sure we try and be more perfect every day that we can.
I know. I faced racism when I was growing up.
But I can tell you, today is a lot better than it was then.
Our goal is to lift up everybody.
Not go and divide people on race or gender or party or anything else.
We've had enough of that in America.
That's why I'm so passionate about doing this.
I don't want my kids growing up where they're sitting there thinking that they're disadvantaged because of a color or gender.
I want them to know that if they work hard, they can do and be anything they want to be in America.